Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
My mother has a saying
for this sort of thing.
It means "the good person is
indistinguishable from the bad."
♪ Our way back home
Through an endless loop tonight ♪
I've heard my mother say it
a thousand times...
and I've never really thought about it
until that day.
When we got the news.
And then
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
Yo. Jensen. Wake up.
Your dad made waffles.
What did we say about dirty dishes.
Justin?
You have lasagna over there
from. like. four nights ago.
You're not
Dr. Fleming discovering penicillin.
Dude. no one ever understands your jokes.
Oh. shit. I'm late. I've gotta get Ani.
Are you allowed to do that?
We have this thing for robotics.
And I wait at the bottom of the hill.
What happened to your back?
Huh?
Oh. are there...
Uh. Homecoming. yeah. um...
You know. the fight and everything.
Weren't you wearing pads?
Yeah. but football. you know?
Aren't you going to be late?
No shower today?
They didn't build us a shower on purpose.
So we'd have to go in there every day.
Forgot my towel.
Uh. that's Zach.
Gotta go.
What the fuck?
Fuck!
Shit.
Good morning. Clay.
Uh...
good morning. Is everything okay?
I'm afraid not.
Difficult time here this morning.
What brings you by?
I'm... picking up a friend.
Which friend is that?
Ani...
- Achola?
- I see.
I don't suppose you've remembered
anything else that might help us out?
You know.
since you last spoke to Deputy Standall.
No. No. sir.
Well. listen. You take care of yourself.
I'm sure we're gonna be talking again
real soon.
What the hell?
Today is truly not the day
to break the rule!
What happened?
They found a body.
In the river.
Jesus!
Bryce?
Mrs. Walker is going to the morgue
to do the ID.
Oh. God!
So. what? They think maybe...
maybe it was an accident?
Do you think this many police cars turn up
when it's an accident?
Maybe he killed himself?
Maybe...
They think it was murder.
They do.
But kids don't kill kids. right?
I mean. like school shootings
and drugs and stuff.
but not like that. not here.
Didn't you want to kill him?
I didn't mean it!
Did you feel it?
We can't talk about this here.
My mother could come outside.
I'm in trouble.
Right? I'm in trouble.
You came by here last week
and you threatened to kill him
and his mother heard you.
And now he's dead.
I think we're in trouble.
We are or I am?
Did they say what happened?
That's all we know.
I just wanted to get to you guys
before it hits the news.
Sooner or later.
everyone looks guilty.
And given the right circumstances.
the right motivation...
who knows what any of us might do?
Fuck!
Hey.
Are you...
Are you okay?
No. man. No. I'm not. I'm...
I'm fucking sad.
You...
You are?
Yeah. I've known him since I was eight.
He was the first person
that gave a shit about me.
the first person to look after me. man.
He was my fucking brother.
I feel like he didn't look out for you.
though.
Dude. you don't know
what you're talking about. Okay. Clay?
You don't know everything.
You think you have this idea that...
You knew what you knew.
He was a fucking person. Clay.
A human being.
Now he's fucking dead.
Hey.
So. I'm guessing you didn't get chance
to check the news today.
- I hate the fucking news.
- They found Bryce.
He's dead.
Javier. can you watch the shop
for a couple hours?
Wait. what are you doing?
I'm gonna go talk to the cops
before they come back here
so I can get ahead of the story.
What. you're gonna tell them everything?
I'm gonna tell them enough
to keep them off my back.
- I gotta protect my family. Caleb.
- Exactly.
And the more you talk.
the more they'll dig.
and the closer they'll get
to finding out.
Wanting someone dead?
Well. maybe that says less
about who you are
and more about what you have to lose.
Sheriff.
I can't help noticing
I'm in an interrogation room.
It's the only place to talk in private.
Mrs. Walker.
The walls not only have ears.
they have Twitter accounts.
I want to continue
to respect the family's privacy.
I am the family. Sheriff.
Have you seen my husband?
We've spoken with him.
It's his wish
to keep this as quiet as possible.
It's my wish to find the person
who killed my son.
Ma'am. we're moving forward
with the investigation.
but absent further information...
we have to explore...
all possibilities.
Such as?
Was Bryce depressed?
Might he have been despondent
in any way?
I can imagine that returning to Liberty
must've been awfully emotional.
My son did not kill himself.
- Can you tell me just how you know?
- Do you think he would kill himself?
Well...
I think...
I've seen...
that when people are
in extreme circumstances.
they can act out of character.
Sometimes even to a tragic end.
Is there something
you would like to ask me. Sheriff?
Not just yet. Mrs. Walker.
But please. rest assured
that we are working every angle.
And we will find out what happened.
Clay Jensen. Tony Padilla.
Justin Foley. Montgomery de la Cruz.
Jessica Davis...
I know these names by heart now.
Sheriff.
You should. too.
Once you stop to think about it.
I think it's entirely possible
for a kid to kill another kid.
And if a killer sat beside you in class.
you might not ever know it.
May I have your attention. please?
Moments ago.
we received some extremely sad news
from the Evergreen County Sheriff.
Former Liberty student Bryce Walker
was found this morning
and has been confirmed dead.
Shit! Jesus!
This is the only information
we have at this time.
but we ask that you keep his family
in your thoughts today.
Crisis counseling services
will be available for all students.
and we encourage everyone
who may need help to reach out.
Teachers...
Jessica Davis probably had more reason
than anyone to want Bryce dead.
Was it such a stretch to wonder
whether she might have taken justice
into her own hands?
- Jess. wait up.
- What do you want. Alex?
I want to see how you're doing.
How am I doing?
Everybody's looking at me
like I must be glad that he's dead.
Like I did something.
Yeah. but you didn't do anything.
- Jess...
- Don't!
Okay? Just don't.
We need to talk about Jessica.
What about Jessica?
I don't know if this is anything.
I really hope it isn't anything.
but I found this in Bryce's room
last night.
You were in his room?
Is that your takeaway?
It means that he was writing to her
just before he died.
Writing to her why?
"Can't stop thinking about you.
Replaying that night in my mind."
Jesus!
He was thinking about her
and he planned to reach out.
And if he did...
The note didn't prove anything exactly.
You really think she could do it?
But it raised a question.
You really think she couldn't?
If Bryce had actually given it
to Jessica.
what would she have done?
Finally. as your outgoing
student body president.
it is my distinct honor to announce
next year's president-elect...
Jessica Davis!
Thank you.
Uh...
thank you. Uh...
I know my speech was...
Well. people had different opinions
on my speech.
Boo.
And yeah. the administration
did talk to me about it.
but the thing they were mostly upset about
was the profanity.
I was like. "Seriously?
That's what you heard?"
Fuck that!
I'm pissed off.
I'm gonna be pissed off
until things actually change.
Until the predators
and the rapists are gone for good.
Fuck rapists! Fuck Bryce Walker!
Never again.
I think she's awesome...
and sort of terrifying.
You're right.
Um...
Look. the other day.
you tried to warn me about Bryce.
I thought I knew the whole story. but...
when that girl shouted Bryce's name
just now...
Jessica never told you?
She never said who it was.
And you never put it together?
I didn't think it was a girl at Liberty.
I didn't know the whole history.
Yeah.
there's a whole history.
I'm sorry...
that I shut you down.
It's all right. I...
I have this thing where I think
I know what's best for everybody.
and I keep not learning my lesson
that I actually don't know shit.
I think you know a lot.
You know the whole history.
Where have you been?
Practice ended two hours ago.
Since when do you care
what I do with my time?
I've always cared. Bryce.
Now I need to pay more attention. don't I?
You're not living
with your father anymore.
Yeah. I'm aware.
And now you're living with yours.
Yes. and if I'd ever spoken
to him the way...
You're on lockdown.
You go to class. you go to practice.
you come home.
Okay. I'm sorry.
What is this?
You check in with me or Amara Josephine
when you get home.
And you hand over your keys at night.
Okay. that's a little excessive.
don't you think? I'm not a child.
This is not a negotiation.
Hitting the books again?
Or can I tempt you
with a round of poker?
I promise I'll go easy on you.
Sorry. finals. Maybe next time.
How's life at Liberty. by the way?
Do they...
ever talk about me over there?
What do you imagine they would say?
I don't know.
But if I were you.
I wouldn't believe everything you hear.
I don't believe anything I hear.
I only believe what I see.
I never told Jessica
that I lived in Bryce's house.
She never found out.
- In his guest house?
- On his grandfather's property.
He didn't live there
when my mum took the job.
Obviously I would've told you ages ago.
but...
I never made the connection
until yesterday.
We never talked about it.
Yeah. I know. I know. I just...
I didn't tell you about it
because with you I had the chance to.
like. not be the victim.
I just could be strong.
That's how you are. To me.
Does he ever try to talk to you?
Uh... no. not really. I don't see him.
I'm not allowed in the main house.
Okay. You have to be careful.
- I always am.
- Promise me.
I promise.
I didn't know what Jessica would do
if she ever saw Bryce.
but I didn't think it would be good.
I'd like to welcome our new
members to the... Student Council.
And I'd like to begin discussion on the...
spring Powder Puff
Flag Football fundraiser.
Actually. I'd like to start discussion
with Liberty hosting
a spring
Take Back the Night event.
Okay.
let me remind you that Powder Puff
is our primary spring fundraiser.
But girls in bikinis playing football
isn't really why I was elected. so...
You can't mess with Powder Puff.
- I'm a coach this year. Pow!
- Yeah.
Sit down. You're out of order.
- What a bitch.
- Total bitch.
Hey. inappropriate. guys.
Inappropriate.
That was pure bullshit.
- And fucking Bolan?
- I know!
Casey. right?
Yeah.
Listen. you are way too much
of a badass
to let the fucking Powder Puff keep you
from toppling the patriarchy.
This whole system is so fucked!
I just... I need to find a way around it.
Or dismantle it.
Yes! Blow it up.
I'm so in!
Okay. this is exciting.
Alarming. but very exciting.
Yeah. So. where do we start?
Jessica was angry.
So. here's what we're gonna do...
We needed to know just how angry.
She's never here this late.
Is she waiting for someone?
What?
Look.
I don't know anything about anything.
I haven't seen Bryce since court
and I don't know
how I feel about it. okay?
Okay. yes. Sorry.
- So. he hadn't been in touch or anything?
- Why do you care?
About Bryce?
- I guess I don't really.
- Good.
So drop it.
She's lying.
I know for a fact she's talked to Bryce
since court because I saw it happen.
Um. I guess we could...
We could talk in here.
Uh...
do you wanna sit down?
I could get you a drink. or...
No. thank you.
I came
because I wanted you to know that...
I'm doing really great.
That's great to hear.
I mean. it's taken me a while.
because for a long time
I thought there was something in me
that was. like...
permanently broken.
I don't know what to say.
Yeah. clearly.
But I don't need you to say anything.
I just need you to know
that you didn't break me.
Or I guess the parts that you did break.
I'm rebuilding them
and they'll be stronger
than they were ever before.
Okay.
Okay?
- What do you want me to say? It...
- I want you to say...
I want you to know what you did.
Everything you fucking did.
To me.
to Hannah. to Chloe.
to who the fuck knows who else.
- I know what I did.
- You have no fucking idea!
I went too far.
You're a fucking psychopath!
I mean. you destroyed lives.
I hope that's not true.
I'm the president of the student body now.
did you know that?
I heard about that. yeah.
Congrats.
I have a family who are amazing.
My friends are amazing.
I have a boyfriend who cares about me
and treats me really well.
I'm happy for you. truly.
I only want the best for you. Jess.
Yeah...
but it's weird.
because no matter what I do...
you're still on top of me.
and I still can't breathe.
Jess. wait.
I saw things around that house.
I saw Bryce and Jessica.
But I mostly steered clear of Bryce.
Because of Jessica.
I avoided him almost entirely.
Go fish.
You don't say "go fish."
you say "I'll take two."
I'll take two.
Preferably diamonds. please.
Thank you.
Oh. thank you very much!
You have a terrible poker face.
Unless I'm messing with you.
Are you messing with me?
I've agreed to play poker with you.
that's your first clue.
I see you.
and...
raise.
So. you don't have any friends.
What makes you say that?
You're playing poker with the help
on a Friday night.
Maybe I thought we could be friends.
But you know the world doesn't work
that way.
Your mother employs mine.
Like. I have to be nice to you.
Don't pout.
It doesn't mean we can't be friendly.
We just have to be honest
about your situation.
And what do you think that is?
I think...
you're lonely.
I think you don't know who you can trust.
I think you've hurt people
and you're trying to change.
but it's not easy 'cause it never is.
You know a lot.
So. it must be clear to you that
I'm essentially fucked in this world.
That's not clear at all.
I match you.
And I raise you.
Okay. it's "I see you."
Not "match you." "I see you."
I see you.
You're alive.
You're rich.
You're white.
You are in no way fucked.
Well. shit's broken.
So. fix it.
- It's not that easy.
- I know.
Like I said. it never is.
Call.
Go fish.
Holy shit.
That's a straight flush.
So it is.
Beginner's luck. I guess.
Go again?
Yeah. that'd be great. I have to be home
by a certain time.
- It's really lame. but...
- Hey.
That's fine. Hey.
Hey. my parents are both working splits
tonight. so. house to ourselves.
Oh. amazing.
I actually have to study
for Spanish tonight.
Maybe this weekend?
Okay. yeah. Sounds good.
- Cool.
- All right.
- What?
- Nothing.
- Shut up!
- I didn't say anything.
- Say it.
- I just...
It's not my place.
but there didn't seem like a great deal
of passion behind that kiss.
Fuck! Do you think he noticed?
I don't know what boys notice.
You think nothing. and then...
We're having awful sex.
I mean awful.
And I think it's me.
I thought I was ready. but...
you know. all the stuff
that I should feel good about just...
makes me feel nothing.
And he tries so hard. I feel bad.
Maybe you should try figuring it out
on your own first?
What?
You mean. like...
- Masturbate.
- Ssh! Jesus!
So. I'm guessing you've never...
Oh. my God!
I just. I really thought my mom was gonna
ask for a fashion show.
We could've done.
Oh. and invited your mom?
Right.
Well. let's have a look at your options.
Oh. my God! I can't even look.
- Jessica Davis!
- What?
- Listen to me. don't be a child.
- I'm not. I'm not. I just...
It just took me so long
to even start having sex again.
Thing is...
every time I look at my body.
it's still...
like I'm seeing it through his eyes.
Like it's not even mine.
It is your body.
And you're the one who's stuck in there.
so you might as well figure out
how to use the hardware.
- That's really scary.
- You see?
We're figuring out what you like already.
Nothing gross or scary.
I don't even know what to do
with any of this stuff.
Well. I will instruct you.
and then I will leave you to your devices.
- as it were.
- Okay.
Right. let's start with...
Dildo Shaggins.
♪ The black above is dense with stars ♪
♪ Millions of lights ♪
♪ Each one in flames like all of us ♪
♪ Glowing slowly burning out ♪
♪ I am floating in space and time ♪
♪ In the midst of neon lights ♪
♪ Can anybody hear me? ♪
♪ Can you hear my heartbeat? ♪
Holy shit!
Oh. my God!
I've never felt that way with sex before.
have you?
Like you have complete control
over your own body.
It's different when you're by yourself.
No need to worry about
making some embarrassing face.
Oh. my God. and if your boobs
are doing something weird.
Except...
uh...
there is this one part
that didn't totally feel healthy.
I started thinking of someone
that I shouldn't have.
Someone really bad for me.
It's fucked up.
Hey. whatever. It's just a fantasy. right?
It doesn't mean anything.
Well. I think it's part
of this whole thing of. like...
taking back control of my own body.
you know?
Rewriting my own story.
Right. Yeah. like...
you have to think about this person
in order to get them out of your system
for good.
Yeah. Yeah. maybe that's it.
So...
So you're saying all that sex stuff
ended with her...
Maybe sleeping with someone
she shouldn't have.
But she didn't tell you who?
Which leads me to believe
it was someone...
really bad.
Wait. Bryce?
That's... that's insane.
She wanted to reclaim her power.
rewrite her story.
Jesus. Ani.
I know. I know. It's...
No. No. there's no way.
Yeah. but why else would she lie
about seeing him?
Well. because he's dead.
But why not tell us the truth?
Because you lived with Bryce
and I live with Justin.
What if Jessica had acted
on her fantasies
and if things had gone very wrong?
So. how was your first day?
Uh. turns out
I'm a fucking genius at making lattes.
Oh. how come you're all dressed up?
Because...
I have a date.
Mmm?
Kind of a date. I mean. I'm hanging out
with Ani at night some place.
Shit!
You asked her out?
Kind of. It was hard to tell. I...
I asked her if she wanted to eat dinner...
with me and she said yes.
Okay. Yeah. that counts.
Okay. so. don't talk too much.
'cause you tend to get nervous
and then just talk.
Um. don't talk about other girls.
And if she wants to have sex with you
in the Prius. I would say just...
think about it first.
If she wants to what?
What the fuck?
What is it?
Uh. just...
something I gotta deal with.
Where the fuck is the Village Motel?
Don't you have Tyler tonight?
Yeah. I got it.
Okay? Have fun.
Go!
- Thank God! I am so hungry.
- Same.
Mmm.
- Mmm.
- Hmm.
I'm so sorry about that place.
It said "authentic British food" online.
But...
is Britain actually trying
to poison its people
or is that place revenge
for the Revolutionary War?
Sorry. you went online
to find "authentic British food?"
Yeah.
I mean. I also Googled
"What is Kenyan food."
but I just felt kind of racist.
Which. by how you are looking at me.
maybe it is?
Or maybe I'm just talking too much?
Which I was warned is a thing I do.
so I should probably stop.
- But you did say Kenya. right?
- I did.
But I... I hardly know it.
I was only four
when my mum came to the UK.
and then a decade later
we moved to the US. so...
all I know about Kenya is
from what my mum tells me.
Or what she cooks.
which is technically Ugandan.
Yeah. Evergreen definitely doesn't have
a Ugandan restaurant.
No worries. We love mayonnaise.
There's more room here anyway.
Mmm.
I mean. yeah. it's pretty roomy.
Hmm.
I mean. we should probably spread out
a bit. don't you think?
So we can properly do the work.
Do the... the work?
Yeah. the robotics project.
Right after the assignment
you said we should go for dinner.
So I just assumed you meant the...
Project!
Right. yeah. No. that's...
That's obviously what I meant by that.
- Shall we get started?
- Yeah.
I. uh...
made a few sketches...
just to...
Uh. wait...
did you draw these?
Yeah.
Wait. you know Alien Killer Robots?
How's that even possible?
Because I also can read?
No. No one knows AKR. You...
Favorite issue?
You.
- Eighty-five.
- Shut the fuck up!
- Clay?
Tyler. what...
- What are you doing? Where's Justin?
- He never showed.
I just came by to see
if maybe he was working.
and that it was me
who mixed things up. but. um...
Wait. so you're just
- by yourself?
- Yeah.
- Well. should I just go home?
- Oh. no.
- Don't be silly. Join us.
- Are you sure?
I mean. 'cause it kind of feels like
you two are...
on a date. or...
No.
Definitely not a date.
Here. sit down.
Okay.
Thanks.
I knew it.
You totally thought it was a date.
Whatever. Can we focus?
You said you think it was Bryce
who texted Justin that night.
Why?
Tyler found you.
then I went home and I found Bryce.
I didn't put it together then.
but he absolutely mentioned Justin.
Said that he'd been drinking
at the Village Motel?
If Bryce told Justin about Jessica...
We should definitely talk to him.
What time does he get off?
What do we even say? I mean.
do we just ask him what happened?
Maybe we give him an out.
say it was self-defense. or...
they were fighting
and Bryce hit his head.
Wait. look.
Come on!
- Do we follow them?
- I dunno.
I think we have to follow them
so that we have the option
of having followed them.
Because if we don't. we won't.
I totally understood that.
which is frightening. but yes.
All right.
Tyler. keep your head up.
Come on. Tyler. You got this!
Whoa! All right. Ty!
Keep it comin'. Breathe!
Watch your balance.
Shit!
That's it.
All right. Ty!
All right. I'm callin' it.
You win. You win!
I won!
You're on fire today. Tyler.
- On fire and fast as hell.
- Yeah.
You were fighting like you were angry.
Angry?
No.
No. happy.
You fought free. What's that about?
Well...
Well. it was fucking awesome.
Let's hit the heavy bag.
- Hey.
- What's up?
That was a...
That was a good day. right?
It was a very good day.
Um...
Give me five minutes. I'm gonna
help them close up and I'll get you home.
Oh. hey. So. listen.
I had a question for you. um...
When you and Clay got rid of all...
After Spring Fling...
When you guys got rid of everything.
where did you. like. have it?
How did you do it?
Well. like we said back then.
we think it's best that you don't know.
I know. But. you know. it's been a while
and everything's good.
so I was just...
- Could you just tell me how you did it?
- Tyler. why do you want to know?
Well. I was just...
So. here's the thing. um...
- I... I kept a gun.
- You what?
And I didn't tell you guys because.
I mean. I had a feeling you'd get mad.
- You had a feeling? Yeah.
- Yeah. and...
Well. yeah. So. here's the thing. um...
I kept it 'cause I thought
I might need it.
Now I know I don't need it.
I want to get rid of it.
Let's go get it right now.
No. I mean. I want to get rid of it.
You guys have done everything.
I don't want you to handle this. too.
Oh. we're handling it.
I am taking you home to get it right now.
Wait. wait! No. no. no!
I... Actually. I can't do it right now.
my parents are there.
Let's go...
now.
Caleb. could I borrow your phone?
Everyone's looking at me asking questions.
It's freaking me out.
Jess. do you think this was a stupid idea
to get together tonight?
I mean. just everything is
so fucking crazy right now and...
I need you
to keep your shit together. okay?
I can't have you falling apart on me.
Shit.
What the fuck?
Hello.
What the hell are you doing here?
Come inside and close the door.
Come on!
Look. Justin. here's the thing.
Whatever happened.
we can take care of it.
I'm sure it was self-defense.
or at least we can make that case.
Just stay calm.
Hey. I'm super calm.
What the fuck are you talking about?
We don't think
anyone's going to judge you.
- With all the history...
- How'd you find us?
- Did you follow us?
- Yeah. why did you find us?
We know what you did!
What both of you did.
And we want to help.
Wait. help with what?
With whatever we need to do
to keep you guys out of prison.
Prison?
Dude. what do you think we did?
You got back at Bryce!
For what was going on
with him and Jessica.
What?
It was Bryce. wasn't it?
He was the one you were talking about
when you said
you had to rewrite your story.
And I'm sure we can explain this in a way
that makes you both innocent.
You were. like. under Bryce's spell
and you confronted him...
Crime of passion.
I'm so sorry.
You thought I was sleeping with Bryce?
That's seriously fucked up.
We know that you saw Bryce
at the house.
And we know that Justin confronted him
last summer.
Is this...
not what happened?
No.
It's not.
What the fuck is this place?
Ah. Mom won't let me drink
at home anymore.
What's up? What do you want?
Sit down. Grab a beer.
You said it was important.
You said it was about Jess.
It's about Jess.
It's about us.
It's about a lot of shit. Sit.
No. fuck you. What about Jess?
She came to see me.
No. she didn't.
She seems like she's doing great.
Dude. if she's coming to see you.
she's not doing great.
- And if you're fucking lying to me...
- I've never lied to you.
You have. though.
Every time you called me brother.
My dad left. Did you know that?
My mom can't stand to be around me.
Chloe dumped me.
Hillcrest's a fucking nightmare.
Am I supposed to feel sorry for you?
You want me to give you my fucking list?
- You have a family.
- Hey. I've never had a family.
I was your family.
For a while.
I'd do anything to get that back.
Is that what we're doing here?
You give me a couple of beers
and I'm your brother again?
- Just like old times?
- I fucked up. okay?
With you. with Jess...
with everybody.
Yeah...
you did.
And I let you do it. and I...
I let you keep doing it.
And you and I. we're just...
gonna have to keep living with that.
I know about Spring Fling.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I know what Tyler tried to do.
And I know you guys covered it up.
I saw you and Jess run out of the gym
that night. so I looked out the side door.
I saw everything.
The cops pulled me in
because. you know.
I'm the rapist. so...
But I kept my fucking mouth shut.
I didn't say a word.
And I'm not going to.
So. what do you want?
I don't want anything from you.
Then why'd you text me?
Listen...
Don't talk to me again.
Stay away from Jessica.
Stay away from her fucking neighborhood.
from wherever she might be.
or I will fucking kill you!
Jesus. why didn't you tell me?
Because I believed him
and I didn't want to freak you out.
How could you think I would do that?
With Bryce? It's disgusting.
Jessica...
I'm sorry.
And you spied on me?
I saw you once at the house.
I wasn't trying to spy on you. I swear.
So. that day you went over there...
that was the last time
you ever talked to him?
You have ten minutes
from the theater is empty.
All trash in can. Sweep up any popcorn.
Wet mop for coke or slushies.
Gum off seats.
Trash. sweep. mop. gum. Got it.
I don't think
you're taking this seriously.
I totally am. I need this job
and I want to do it right. Miss Davis.
I'm. like. two years older than you.
And I get why you might think
I'm gonna be an asshole
- or something.
- Oh. you get it?
What exactly do you get?
I get the feeling that
you're judging me by my friends.
Of course I am.
Everybody gets judged by their friends.
Yeah. I just...
I kinda wish you wouldn't.
Putty knife. For the gum. Go!
Awesome.
Hey.
What do you want?
I just...
I wanted to say
that I know that I hurt people.
that I fucked up a lot of people's lives.
Uh-huh.
And I wanted to apologize.
Oh. you did? That's nice.
I talked to Justin...
to apologize to him.
and he just said that if I come anywhere
near your neighborhood. he'll kill me.
So I'm literally risking my life
by being here right now.
Well. then you'd better go.
I don't know what you want me
to fucking do or say.
or I... or what the fuck...
but I am sorry.
And I will be sorry
until the day that I die
for what happened that night
at your party.
And for everything that happened after.
What happened was that
you raped me while I was unconscious
- and then lied about it to everybody!
- Jess...
I'm not that person anymore.
I don't believe that.
I don't think you do either.
I don't need an apology from you.
I realized
I don't need a goddamn thing from you.
Why don't you work on
what it is you need?
Jessica had talked to Bryce once more.
But not to work through her sexual trauma.
She found other ways
of reclaiming her power.
- Justin. hey.
- Hey. What's up?
I don't need you to fight my fights
for me. okay? I can take care of myself.
- What are you talking about?
- Bryce said you threatened him?
Fuck me!
I didn't. I just...
I just told him to leave you alone.
I don't need your protection.
I don't need anything from anyone. okay?
Okay. Yeah. I get it. I'm sorry.
Why do people go messing
with who they shouldn't mess with?
I don't know. I really am. I'm so...
Don't defend me.
Don't talk about me.
Don't talk to me ever.
You look so beautiful right now.
Shut up!
This isn't working for me.
What?
It's just...
sex. my body...
trying to be in a relationship.
It's not fair for you
to be dragged along
on this roller coaster ride with me.
You're not dragging me.
I love you.
I don't want to hurt you. Alex.
We can take a break.
Maybe you need some time off.
No.
I need this to be done.
I think maybe you should go.
I am really sorry
that I thought it was Bryce.
Justin's bad enough. right?
No. No. it's your body.
you can do what you want with it.
I thought maybe that's why
you bailed on me at Homecoming.
- Because you thought I was a hypocrite.
- No! No. that was just...
I chickened out.
I'm not as brave as you are.
I don't know about that.
I'm. like. the girl who's all about
taking down the bad guys.
So. what's everyone gonna think
when they find out I've been hooking up
with the guy who let me get raped.
That's your business...
and yours alone.
No one else has to know.
It's actually been...
really hard not to be able
to talk about any of this stuff with you.
Well.
the good news is now you can.
I don't even know how to explain it.
I mean...
once I started thinking
about Justin. I just...
couldn't stop.
Hello and welcome to Monet's.
How can I help you today?
Nobody says that here.
I need to talk to you. Now.
Okay. I have a break in.
like. ten minutes. so...
Justin. I need to talk to you now.
Jess. fuck. I've missed you so...
For the first time in so long.
sex wasn't this thing where I was just
going through the motions anymore.
And then it started
to get a little bit...
kinky.
Oh?
So. what are we doing here?
- We're exploring.
- Okay.
I'm figuring my shit out.
- Are you good with that?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. totally good with that.
- Okay.
I started to realize
I like deciding
where my body goes during sex.
I like being the one in control.
Oh!
♪ This baby don't cry ♪
- Oh. shit! Fuck! Fuck. it's Clay.
- Shit!
We gotta hide. Let's go!
I'm hiding. you live here!
- Go!
- Yeah. right. right. Okay.
Why'd you lock the door?
Um. I'm just...
Just kind of in the middle of something.
What? It's...
Everyone does it!
That's what that was?
Have you guys ever...
I mean. not on my bed. right?
Oh. no!
- Oh. man!
- Dude.
man. you gotta learn how to chill.
You're never gonna get laid
if you're so squeamish.
Dude. man. my bed. your bed.
And those scratches were...
Yeah. she's just like...
It's rough.
- You...
- Anyway. I am starving.
You want anything from in the house?
- Nah. I'm good.
- Right on.
Justin...
Yeah?
Look. I'm...
I'm sorry that I even thought you could...
you know.
Forget it.
But...
someone killed Bryce.
Yeah.
It's fucked up.
I think my mother was right.
that the good person really is
indistinguishable from the bad.
The trick was trying to tell
who just wanted Bryce dead.
and who could actually kill.
Tony. I'm sorry. I've been. um...
tied up.
What?
What? He... he what?
He said he couldn't grab it
while his parents were home.
Uh. he said he would give it to you
in the morning.
Okay.
Good. No. I'm staying right here.
Later.
But if the killer wasn't Jessica...
then who was it?
♪ Our ascent ♪
♪ My decline ♪
We need to talk.
Okay. not here. I'll call you.
So. you aren't gonna invite me in?
Dude. you ever come back here.
I will kill you.
Like you killed your rich buddy?
Who. out of everyone we knew.
would be most likely to pull the trigger?
For help finding crisis resources.
visit 13reasonswhy. info
♪ Valentine told me who's to go ♪
♪ Feelings he's treasured most of all ♪
♪ The teachers and the football stars ♪
♪ It's in his tiny face ♪
♪ It's in his scrawny hands ♪
♪ Valentine told me so
He's got something to say ♪
♪ It's Valentine's Day ♪
♪ The rhythm of the crowd ♪
♪ Teddy and Judy down ♪
♪ Valentine sees it all ♪
♪ He's got something to say ♪
♪ It's Valentine's Day ♪
♪ Valentine. Valentine ♪
♪ It's in his scrawny hands ♪
♪ It's in his icy heart ♪
♪ It's happening today ♪
♪ Valentine. Valentine ♪
♪ It's in his scrawny hand ♪
♪ It's in his icy heart ♪
♪ It's happening today ♪
♪ Valentine ♪
Well done. Ed. Well done.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org